hello from Japan this is country number
eight for me and I'm very excited to be
here so just arriving now from taipe let
me get through immigration and then uh
we'll go from
there got Mario on the wall
here something going on with my ear from
the uh flight hopefully it resolves
itself
soon okay guys well we are officially in
Tokyo so yes country number eight very
very grateful to be here and that was a
very quick immigration process I
recommend that you fill out the forms
online before you come here uh because
it was just like scan QR codes put your
fingerprints in bang done now I have to
pick up my
Jr pass I bought the Jr pass um so I
need to pick that up and then we're
going to take the train and we're going
to explore Tokyo something's going on
with my ear it's like uh there's water
it feels like there's water in my ear
something to do with the uh elevation my
ear didn't pop I don't know but I need
to ask somebody where the Jr pass is all
right guys I got my uh Japan uh Rail
Pass here took not too long I bought it
I pre purchased it online I was worried
cuz some people say it takes forever but
took me very very short amount of time
have my SIM card it cost me $40 for 15
days unlimited data and now I need to
find a ATM first look at the uh money
here
in Japan nice okay sorry for the
flickering guys but I had to change my
uh settings there so the lights are now
good no more flickering in this video
okay so here's the Jr
East now I need to take the Narita
Express the Jr
line and I was told that I have
to schedule it
I should have scheduled it in advance
truthfully I scheduled a bunch of other
train rides in
advance
so let's see here's my Jr
pass looks like I should probably buy
these one of these sweet
cards but let me
go talk to someone
here maybe I don't have to schedule it I
don't know
do I need a reservation to take the
Narita Express yeah oh I do okay I don't
have a reservation but I have my Jr
pass got
you okay maybe I'll try so are there
multiple ones 445 and then there's there
another another one yes okay all right
thank you so maybe I'll get on 445 maybe
I won't I don't know but it's a
significant cost savings so I better do
it cuz in Uber yes it would probably be
quicker but it would be very expensive
so I've already paid for this uh Jr pass
I might as well take advantage of
[Music]
it
okay oh I made it I just had to run 90
seconds I made it within 90 seconds so
here we
are guys I have to say that was was a
bit stressful but I got it all sorted
within like 90
seconds but we made it so we're on our
way in here to Shinjuku so yes here we
go I was uh struggling with my uh ticket
getting the the reader to read my ticket
and a very friendly uh couple a Japanese
couple really helped me and they pointed
me in the right direction and I got it
so
yes we're in Tokyo baby okay guys well I
I would consider myself to be a a pro
with public transportation up to this
point but I got to tell you this one
here in Japan is stressful so now I'm
doing a
switch and I'm at Tokyo Station I think
I need to go to Marucci line but I don't
I don't know I have to ask somebody I've
asked two people okay guys so I 100%
missed my connecting train here to in
Juku so I think I'm going to go to a
visitor center and see what I can do to
get on another train there but it's been
a long day of travel I'll don't tell you
that much first time I've ever missed a
train I'm actually really good with this
stuff this has been very
confusing and we're in Tokyo Station so
it's
like the biggest
one I
mean can you just feel how crowded it is
here
oh my God so I got it sorted out I got
to go to chwo line one or two I missed
the other one so I got to go to this one
but this we are in the biggest city in
the world and probably the most
busy Metro station in the world if I'm
guessing
Okay very stressful very
stressful
so let's see here okay 20
mean wow guys
okay I mean I can't even walk right now
it's
crazy
um okay I don't see je line
okay Che
line I'm in Shinjuku some very friendly
man helped me out uh to make sure I was
on the right one but now I have a
99-minute walk I just need to find the
right exit it's going to be fun I have
no idea where this is oh
boy this is the most difficult uh Metro
day I've been on I've had here okay does
Google tell
me okay we'll just go out here
okay well that worked thank God
okay well I just need to get the heck
outside I'm I'm tired of being in a
Metro I think I've been in a Metro for
like three 2 hours 3 hours for the first
time ever I missed my
connecting train for the first time in
my life so there you can see sjuku
station okay well this is expert mode
guys this is expert mode um um Uber
would have been easier but much more
expensive so it is what it is now let me
try to find my place but we are here
guys so we are here all
right here we go 8 minutes
so I will be in Tokyo for 2
weeks I do wish I maybe scheduled more
cuz just on the uh Metro in here I was
like man there are so many things I want
to see in Tokyo but there's always a
number two there's always a chance to
come back in any of these places that
you travel so all
right now it is very hot it's very humid
I decided to wear pants instead of
shorts because I heard some horror
stories about immigration and it turns
out that this was literally the easiest
immigration I've had so definitely just
uh apply online like if you're doing if
you're coming to Tokyo just apply do all
of the immigration stuff beforehand
you'll get a QR you just put the QR go
right through easy don't even have to
worry about it but there is something
about like looking presentable at
immigration especially for Japan but
anyway it was unnecessary so I'm going
to put a more comfortable pair of
clothing on and then I'm going to go
probably get a beer and definitely get
some Japanese food because I've only had
airport lounge food and it is 6:30 p.m.
this day started at like 5 a.m. for me
my flight got delayed 90 minutes in
taipe we lose an hour going from taipe
to Japan so I landed here at 3:30 and it
is 6:30 took me 3 hours to get through
the airport buy a SIM card pick up my Jr
pass get money it took an hour and a
half to get in on the first train ride I
missed the second train ride had to
reroute get on a different train now I'm
here okayo that's a lot it's a mouthful
I know but we're in Tokyo so look at
this look at this guys no more
complaining no more
complaining amazing amazing
view Tokyo has been an eternal bucket
list item for me and so I am so happy to
be here okay guys well look at this
really cool
Alleyway I am somewhere right around
here it's called Tokyo
stay there it is okay I didn't realize
like how in the heart of everything I am
let's here it is Tokyo stay let's get
checked in
here all right okay through here and
okay okay guys so we are here so this is
considered a classic business Hotel it's
called a business hotel in Tokyo and
they're typically cheaper okay but
basically this is what you get okay this
is what you get it's a room I'm very
happy with this let's take a look at
what is in here I have no idea what's
this how to use Corby trouser oh it's a
trouser
press all right I'm not going to do that
right
now oh the bed oh yeah it's definitely
hard but you know what we will make do
no complaints cuz we are here we also
have
airon and this should be the bathroom oh
oh whoa I was not expecting this the
bathroom's almost as big as the entire
room wow I was
expecting a crazy small bathroom um and
you know what I'm super excited for the
Japanese toilet game I'm not going to
lie okay so if you don't know in Japan
these crazy toilets this this is how you
work the toilet over here so I have no
idea it's going to take a minute for me
to understand how to use this Walkin
shower oh my hello and here we are so
this room cost me
$89 or $90 a night yes I know I'm not
joking you heard that right $89 or $90 a
night because I am in Shinjuku U I'm
staying here three nights this is like
one of the best places in Tokyo
to stay Shinjuku and Shibuya those are
the two places they're the most
expensive places other than Ginza so
Ginza shuku uh Ginza Shinjuku and
Shibuya are the most expensive places to
stay because they're probably the most
Lively energetic active Central areas so
that's why you can expect to get
something like this for $90 a night
however and I'm very proud of this I'll
be in Tokyo for 2 weeks I think it's
like 15 days um um 14 or 15 days and my
total spend per night for two weeks in
Tokyo is $79 a night so I was able to
get the spend down by doing a
combination of Airbnb and hotels all
right and let's take a look at this view
here we even got a trouser press guys
right there what is a trouser press I
don't even know do I wear trousers of
course I do anyway here's the view not
much but you know what zero complaints
from
Mah let's go let's go explore
Tokyo hey guys so here's the free
accessories that comes with the room
toothbrushes toothpaste all of the stuff
like
coffees and then we also have these
famous Japanese vending machines here
first look at them so you can get
yourself a Kieran beer 150 yen is a
dollar so that would mean that 300 is2
$2 so that would mean that this
is about $
2504 uh $3 maybe this is like
$3 but yeah cool cool cool cool so I
don't have a plan other than I'm going
to go
explore shuku and I might even head over
to shabuya Crossing which is the famous
Crossing we'll see I don't know I'm
feeling it one of these nights I don't
even really want to bring up the map I
just want to walk I just want to walk
and I want to see what's out here
so stressful day but we're here look at
all these little uh
cafes could be quite challenging to
order but you know since I'm only in
Shinjuku for 3 days I three nights I do
want to like pick wisely I want I want
to Choose Wisely on the restaurants so
yeah this is like a special place now I
can always come back because where I'm
staying next is close to a Metro so the
metro in Tokyo you can get anywhere you
need to go but uh yeah I'm I'm right
here in chinuku for 3 days so I might as
well take advantage but just look at
this street guys oh man and I
suspect every street you turn down is
going to be really cool
so so yeah I'm sure there's amazing
stuff down here
and grilled pork looks really good I
have to say some people have told me
that it can be the interactions can be a
little cold in Japan but I'll tell you
what I have not experienced that I have
experienced very friendly people so far
uh cuz I've been I got legitimately lost
on my way in here and without the people
I talked to I would have been really
confused so for My Thai friends Chang
singha Saigon Lao so we've got a
Southeast
bar
there I mean it's first night we have to
go the bowl of ramen right is that not
is that not what you do got more vending
machines here I will probably do a
vending machine video or do we have to
get a sapro you tell me sapro or Kieran
what is the what is the one I think
sapro is a more
premium I'm at the point where I just
want to dip into one of these
restaurants get a food and some beer
cuz it's where I'm at but I want to make
the most of it you know do you feel me
do you feel me okay here we
go all right let's go with
this okay
spicy
spicy guys I got a spicy Ramen and I got
to say oh does it look good let's try
the garlicky broth
spicy very spicy but very
good the Chopsticks here careful I don't
put my elbows on the the
table okay I think I will get uh beer
number two at this Ale House here so let
me see what they have all right well
cheers again they had Kieran on draft I
did not they did not have sapro on draft
I'm sure I'll have many sapros
here okay guys while I've been sitting
there looking at this vending machine I
was drinking this beer so we've got a
100 yen water I think I'm going to need
some water but we've I want to see what
else is over here so got isotonic water
I've got 100 yen here I don't know if it
takes 50 Yen coins or not but by the way
this is
incredible uh
calus uh which is like a uh it's like a
fermented like uh yogurt
drink but all right let's see here okay
it does take 50 Yen
coins
okay so we put 100 in here and what do
we
do okay
oh
okay let's get this open so it's called
picnic
water picnic
water it's good so I was going to go to
shabuya Crossing tonight but you know
I've been on a Metro for like hours
today I don't feel like going back to
the metro station today I really don't
it was just too much Metro so I'm going
to go over to Golden guy which is a
place that has like hidden bars and
basically these bars are very special
only certain amount of people are
allowed in each bar so like the bar
might be capped at like 10 people only
10 people can be in at a time and
foreigners are not allowed in every bar
it's a very special place so we're going
to go over to Golden guy and we'll see
if we can get a seat I don't know
so not only do can you be denied entry
into into a golden guy bar but I don't
think they're going to like filming so I
will try we'll see how far we get but I
really don't feel like taking the metro
again so that's where I'm at looks like
one of these Ramen spots where you order
you order from the machine and they you
go in and you uh pick up the order
pretty cool I'll have to maybe try it
while I'm
here looks like you like I said looks
like you you pick the one you want I
guess you get a token or a ticket and
then you go in and they serve it to you
like no
contact so Google Maps tells me that
it's right around here so I have no idea
what that says it's in Japanese but you
can see like there are a bunch of little
shops down there and basically these are
like little hidden bars that have like
you just literally some some people just
you're not allowed to go in you just
have to see if you're allowed in
um we'll see I don't
know I'm going to try guys I'm going to
try so yeah like down here I'm sure
that's
one okay death match in
hell is this a golden Guy this is golden
guy yeah this this whole area yeah you
can go like down there down there down
there it's like a little network of okay
thank you guys thank
you
okay so here we
go death match in Hell seems pretty cool
no cover charge you guys get the idea
here
look so like that guy was saying it's
like a little network of bars and shops
and each one has a different theme
love you oh my gosh this is so cool I'm
going to have to go down all of
them I wonder where that goes probably
somewhere cool
[Music]
Hello wow I'm blown away I mean I've
seen this on
YouTube but
to see to be here in person is amazing
500 yen cover charge okay so if you're
going to go there you better
drink okay oh
wow and uh keeps going farther wait I
want to go this
way oh very uh
a lot of uh foreigners
here oh wow by the way I'm going to get
some Instagram photos here so make sure
you follow me on Instagram make sure you
hit subscribe it would really help me
out I'd really appreciate it less than
8% of you are
subscribed this one's like
aquarium
themes okay I want to go back down that
other
Street yeah I mean this is like one of
these things where there are no words
necessary I hope hope you guys can see
how amazing this is yeah I don't know
what's going on in there no okay
photography prohibited I can't go in
there um
some of these no cover charge cash
only some of these I think you can find
yourself in you can get yourself into
some things I think here if you catch my
drift not not not endorsing that in any
way
but oh you get pizzas here I'm noticing
like lots of pizza here in uh
Tokyo lots of pizza
available okay so that might be golden
guy but I want to see what's down here
and then I think we're going to dip into
one of those shops we get ourselves a
golden guy beer but there's something
that looks cool down here so I want to
see it all these Neon Lights caught my
eye so Wow first and foremost just look
down here it's like a grass walkway it's
like a I don't know it's a
walkway uh might have to take that back
because I'm very intrigued is this this
whole area golden
guy oh my gosh guys okay photos are are
incoming I know five words Japanese
onashas which means please so when you
order something you can point and say
onashas what else do I know Su miman
which means excuse
me orato orate
goas and or got
of course Kwa and there's also
Kwa uh death
match so that's what I Know cover cover
for foreign visitors well I like that
that is very nice that is very nice
maybe we go there no photo okay I got to
be careful not everybody's going to want
this if I can't bring you in I'm not
going to bring you in I'm just telling
telling you right
now English
Okay English
okay oh good bar good good bar
okay it's here oh is it here okay you
you pick my seat for me okay all right
hi okay thank
you all right guys I'm continuing this
first day in Japan video here during the
next evening and we're going to go
explore around the Shinjuku station area
in fact we're just going to explore more
of Shinjuku I'm going to be doing
shabuya Crossing in another video so
yeah there are a couple really cool
shops it seems like over here that I'm
excited to check out so this video is
picking up after you uh last saw me go
into the golden guy area and I will tell
you that you will be sure to make
friends if you decide to go in one of
those bars it was an incredible time
last night and yeah I'd highly recommend
you check out golden guy if you are
coming to Tokyo it's an unforgettable
experience so you can just take a look
at this street it's
absolutely beautiful at night and
there's something about Tokyo at night
that I really wanted to capture in this
first day in Tokyo video because one
thing I want to highlight is that Tokyo
is one of the world's safest cities so
this is a place where you can absolutely
explore at any time of time of the day
uh for sure so it's just something uh to
keep in
mind you know I always like to bring in
population uh statistics so Tokyo is
estimated to have around 37 million
people that's if you take the entire
metro area which puts it at the world's
largest city and um it
is very evident when you are walking
around especially in the public
transportation areas so yeah now one of
the things that I would like to do here
now we're not in aih Habra but one of
the things I would like to do here is
maybe go into like a bookstore or like a
used CD shop or use electronic shop
because I believe there are some in this
area so yeah that might be something
that we get into here but right now
we're just going to
explore uh around here for right now I
really like the energy here
so yeah over here looks like we've got
like a shoe
shop um looks like all different types
of
Brands you can pick up shoes lots of
like clothing
areas and this is one of these things
where I don't even really want to bring
up the map I kind of just want to walk
around you can see the street here is
made for
walking and right there is JR East which
is that very
stressful Metro Station that I'm sure
I'll get used to by the time I am done
here this feels like a relatively
upscale area here you know honestly a
lot of Tokyo I have a lot more of Tokyo
to explore in my life and I think it
would take a lifetime truthfully but
this feels like pretty a relatively
upscale area and this area is very
interesting because it's uh a mix of
local eateries
restaurants and also retail shopping and
is like one of these things where you
just you want to go in every shop you
want to go in absolutely every shop and
check everything out like just look at
this this neon sign it looks
incredible so at least to me I don't
know if you guys find that interesting
but I do I don't know what the words are
but yeah let's continue on so there's a
store called book off I actually did
peek at the map but there's a store
called book off that has uh like used
books this is I believe I don't know but
I believe this is also owned by the same
company that owns hard off which is a an
electronic store where you can buy used
game boys and vintage like Electronics
video games stuff like that and I will
be going to a few of those in in a
future uh video here on this Japan
Series so uh yeah okay so I don't know
if we walk up here we walk down here I'd
rather walk down here but yeah let's see
I am somewhat limited on time I do think
we walk down here so this is even better
I'm somewhat limited on time
because uh the store closes in about 2
hours but H not really I'll it's only
about a 10-minute walk and uh guys look
at this x bar it's called craft beer in
game so I'm assuming you can play like
arcade games I do want to dip into an
arcade at some point so maybe it's the
same thing as here I don't know but
this looks pretty cool look you can win
a uh like candy you can win Candy here
look at
this yeah and I have to say this is a
mix of adults and children playing right
now so it's kind of for all ages
here I mean this is just so
fascinating and beyond anything I've
seen before in this
style look
popcorn I have no idea what this
is oh I don't know I don't know you can
even uh try your luck at getting some
House Blend Starbucks here or massive
Pringles this is essentially
gambling these things almost never
hit but hey oh a Gengar I see a Gengar
in every video you been watching my
Taiwan series
oh look uh Kirby oh my
gosh uh my inner child is really going
to come out here in Tokyo that is for
sure that is for darn
sure and that's a good thing that is a
good thing wonder if there's another
floor to this oh my
gosh look at this oh my God guys have
you ever seen anything like
that what are be interesting things I
seen in this Shinjuku area is that there
are casinos air quotes uh basically
they're gaming arcades but they're
casinos and uh I would like to go in and
play some Blackjack I'm not going to be
able to film uh I also
think uh there will be absolutely no
English speaking there so I don't think
I'd even be able to get to play okay
well this looks very cool I don't know
if that's what I'm looking for but I
think I'm going to probably end up going
in here we see more of these um amazing
vending machines we've got Pepsi
refresher shot or refresh shot I have no
idea what that is I'm not going to roll
the dice on that right now I do think
that some of these coffees that you buy
are hot like they actually come out hot
but I need to know before I
buy um but you can get a shot at some of
the prices
here a bottle of water is is less than a
dollar cuz a dollar 150 N is a dollar so
yeah nice bottle of mineral water for
less than a dollar same with a
Coke and uh
yeah but you can see they're just
everywhere but okay so book off should
be around here
somewhere and just take a look at this
shot here of this street
oh it looks incredible I'm going to take
another photo yes here's book
off okay now how do we get up here okay
it
is oh it looks like uh DVDs and stuff
here
wow I do wonder if they have an English
section
look at
that
wow my God guys look at
this wonder what this novel's
about oh
man oh
Shinigami I do know what a Shinigami is
I have watched Death Note so okay well
let's see what else is here let's see if
there's anything else interesting here
okay up here I think we have like DVDs
oh no these are books okay you've got
the One Piece manga
here he what Arc arcs these are oh I
can't read Japanese I don't know and
take a look they also have um phones for
sale here and you can even buy Nintendo
switches here or other video games
how about this
m64 m64 games Okay so this section I'm
not sure what's going on other than
there's more bleach stuff I think this
is like figurines and like some more
like Anime
stuff like you see like trinkets here
little trinkets
[Music]
we like oh Pokemon cards oh get out of
town guys get out of town got a
m um
wow look at all these cards
guys okay well all that book shopping uh
made me thirsty so we're going to go aad
and get a sparkling water believe that's
sparkling water I hope it is so 120
yen see if I have it
here good
and you can see the ones we can buy
light up the ones that you don't have
enough money for don't light up so
okay I consider myself to be a huge fan
of sparkling
water and
uh yeah let's give this a
taste m
and some fine sparkling
water so guys this is one interesting
thing so you have these coin lockers all
over Japan here so if you like I don't
know if you're in between hotel rooms or
airbnbs you can put your luggage in here
and it looks like it's about 1,000 yen I
don't know how long that is
for I don't know how much 1,000 yen
would get you
but H 's
about $7 $78 something like that but
yeah this is so interesting I've seen
them all over uh Tokyo so far but uh
yeah the vibe here in Japan is just is
unbelievable as I was
walking I looked to my
right and found this cool little Street
here
so
see Gosh guys look
I have no idea what this
is I'm really glad I decided to come
down here well I have read that this is
like a classic thing in Japan where you
go down an Alleyway and there's a
whole culture
here okay well I don't know which way to
go but I think we'll go this
way the smell of food food right now is
so incredible no idea so down here it
seems to be even further going even
farther see the big hot po oh my
gosh
wow yeah this is uh this is next
level I'm really wishing I think we've
got yakatori here or some sort of
skewers really wishing I didn't eat
already because yeah I might have to
come back here
tomorrow Indescribable how cool this
is all right so I'm walking towards
kabucho which is I believe the Korean
town here in Japan uh I believe this is
a place
where uh how do we say extracurricular
activities happen but it's also the
place where I see poker uh tables and
I'm wondering if I can find a place to
play Blackjack I won't be able to take
you with me on that but yeah we'll
see here's a
Pinko and Slot so basically what happens
is you play Pinko which is a game and
you win like
tokens and basically you can exchange
the tokens in the alleyway next to it
for money so it's an
arcade so I would love to play some
binko but I don't think I I don't have
an IC card I need to pick up a sua card
and then I think I can load money on it
I don't know I probably could have asked
them in there but I don't know how to
play it there so I'm not going to play
it right now I do hear some live music
though down here in
kabucho look it lights
up I wonder what it
means
okay okay guys so we have more Pinko
here
and this one seems to be even
[Music]
bigger oh another uh one of these alleys
that you can just get lost
in since
2001 yeah
I don't know I don't know what I'm doing
here I can't read
this and I know you can like press I
don't know I don't know what I'm doing
but
[Applause]
okay well that was a bucket list item
Place SL machines in Tokyo so I lost,
Yen which again I think is like
$7 it was an
experience okay wow this is like what
you see in the movies look at this look
at this this is like what you see in the
movies look at all these signs here Neon
Lights crazy energy going on yeah pretty
incredible
oh Tio station it's like a arcade or
something up
there so here's one of the many famous
uh don
kotes here in
Tokyo uh don kyot is a discount Bargain
shop it's a bargain shop it's a discount
store it's a very interesting
background all right so down this Street
you can really see the uh classic Tokyo
scene here that you see in the
movies and I think I might need to be a
little careful filming here because yeah
I might need to be a little careful
filming here but uh yeah we'll see we'll
see
okay so I am going to snap a photo of
this
street but
this is absolutely
fascinating have more arcades
here okay so I have found myself in a
spot
it is very
interesting
[Music]
here this doesn't even feel real guys
this is a this is such an interesting
place oh man so I actually been walking
the entire time and I missed it there it
is there's the Godzilla head and I think
you can get like a really good
shot of the Godzilla if you go to H
gracery and you go up this um building
here the legendary uh Godzilla head I
think there's another one somewhere like
a statue or
something all right guys well I hope you
enjoyed my first time in Japan video
much more content to come here uh from
Japan and yeah make sure you hit
subscribe hit the like button and I'm
going certainly be talking to you again
soon peace